# Brandy Moreno



## Objective

A motivated Financial Mathematics and Statistics college graduate interested in obtaining a job in order to utilize my critical thinking skills in real world situations, improve the competitive position of the enterprise, and gain industry experience.

#### Education

Geekwise Academy

September 2017- December 2017

B.S. University of California, Santa Barbara

September 2013 - June 2017

Financial Mathematics and Statistics

Graduated: June 2017 Relevant Coursework:

Probability and Statistics

Regression Analysis

Numerical Analysis

- Mathematics of Fix Income Markets
- Introduction to Mathematical Finance
- Applied Stochastic Processes

Selma High School September 2009 - June 2013

Graduated: June 2013

### Experience

Intern, City of Selma Finance Department

August 2016 - September 2016

- Analyze and posted journal entries to appropriate supporting documents and signatures
- Organized and filed account payable invoices and checks
- File prior fiscal year finance records (bank reconciliations, financial reports, state and federal reports, Etc.) and prepare filing system for the current year
- Compile financial data from general ledger reports, spreadsheets, and hard copy documents from storage

Hostess, Denny's

May 2013 - September 2013

- Greet and seat customers by guiding them to an assigned table, or communicating delays
- Accountable for the register
- Train incoming hostesses on register software and other hostess duties

#### Skills

Software: Microsoft Office

Programming languages: Python, R, SAS, Matlab, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Angular